2 3 4
MAN: Two, three, four...
你又来了
* Here you come again*
你说你是我的朋友
*And you say that you're my friend*
但我知道你的目的
But I know why you're here*
她想知道我的感受
火 She wants to know how I feel*
告诉她我很开心
Tell her that I am happy
告诉她我很欢愉
*Tell her that I am gay*
告诉她我心甘情愿
*Tell her Iwouldn't have it*
别无他想
*Any other way*
人们都在说
People have been talking*
不 这这这 这太蒂谬
Woman No tha tha that s just that s ridiculous.
我都说了 它又变成行星了
Woman 2: I'm telling you, it's a plainet again.
冥王星一直都是行星
Pluto was always a planet.
不 有段时间不是 现在又是了
No, it wasn t. Now it is again.
你这就好像是在跟我说
This is like when you tried to tell me
草莓是坚果一样
a strawberry is a nut.
-草莓就是坚果 -不是的
Strawberry is a nut. - Irene: No.
种子长在外面的都是坚果
Anything with seeds on the outside is a nut?
-比如覆盆子-是坚果
A raspberry? - A nut.
我恨死你了
I hate your cunt heart.
-我的炸土豆丸子好了 -不错
My tots are done Oh, whoopie.
所以我们今晚看什么
So, what are we going to watch tonight?
你想继续看《亢奋》吗
You want to keep going with"Euphoria"?
那些觉得是自己发明了做爱的小鬼吗 不用了 谢谢
Kids who think they invented fucking? No, thank you.
靠 他妈的 弗莱彻家的把遥控器拿走了
Oh shit. Goddamn Fletchers have the remote.
喂 弗莱彻家的 我们要看《创智赢家》
Joyce: Hey, Fletchers. We're gonna watch "Shark Tank. "
少数服从多数
Majority rules the remote.
服从个屁
Majority rules my foot up your ass.
这什么垃圾节目
What is this garbage?
所以你看完了《奎恩茨福德郡谋杀案》
Joyce: So you finish"Quaintsfordshire Murders"
还想让我们看挪威的死人吗
and nowfyou want us to care about who dies in Norway?
-嘘 -凶手是金发那个
Fletchers: Shh! - Irene: The blonde did it.
死婊子们
Bitches.
艾琳 你的体征检测器充电了吗
Ooh, Irene, did you charge your heartcuff?
当然了 比利
I sure did, Billy.
很好笑 因为我这里看到
That's hilarious because, um, I'm showing:
艾琳 零格电 没有信号
Irene. Zero percent. No transmission.
你想监控我的一举一动
Oh, you want to track my every movement,
这样每次我去厕所
so you know every time I go to the bathroom
你都可以靠想象我
so you can jerk it to the knowledge
来打飞机
that I'm pooping.
这不是定位系统 艾琳
It's not a GPS, Irene,
它只是监控你的生命体征而已
all it does is track your vital signs.
我不会让你们像给狗装芯片一样监控我的
Not gonna chip me like some dog.
汪
Woof!
最后一次机会
Betty: Last chance.
最后一个动物园旅行的报名机会
Last chance to sign up for the zoo trip.
当然了 好极了
Oh, sure. Great.
但是等等
Oh, wait, though.
但我们赶得及回来换尿布
Will we get back in time to change our diapers
看天线宝宝吗
and to watch"Teletubbies"?
我们不是小婴儿 贝蒂
We're not fuckin' toddlers, Betty.
早见过鸸鹋了
We've seen emus before.
如果你们不能
Betty: If you can't make an effort
更加积极参与社区活动
to be a more positive community presence,
我可能得向管理部门
I may have to report
举报你们的非法药物种植了
your illegal drug plants to the administration.
不不不
No, no, no, no.
-不不不 -我们那是救命药
No, no, no. Our life- saving medicine.
我知道你没得青光眼
I know you don't have glaucoma.
而且我很讨厌
And I, and I hate this
你们玩的这诡异的中国游戏
witchy Chinese game you're playing.
这都什么 咒符吗
What are these, runes?
没错 贝蒂
That's right, Betty.
我们是喜欢药物的撒旦崇拜者
We're Satanists who love drugs.
她真是烦死人了
What a fucking cop.
好了
Alright now.
我们把你安排在了三楼
So we have you on our third floor.
那里是医疗区
That's our medical care unit.
我可以带你转转我们这里
I can give you a full tour of the facilities.
然后帮你戴上体征检测器
: And get you set up on our heartcuff system.
但我先送你上去安顿好吧
But I'll let you get settled in first.
你和我想的一样吗
You thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
我们得把那狗娘养的杀了
We have to kill that motherfucker.
倾倒
*Comin'down*
Comin' down*
我为之倾倒
*Yes, I'm comin'down*
满意了吗
We happy?
倾倒 倾倒 倾倒
*Imcomin'down, down, down, down, down*
*I'mcomin'down, down, down, down, dowq*
心脏病发
*Comin'down with a heartache*
我没病 却体温火热
*I ain't sick but I got a fever*
血压升高
Blood pressure's runnin'high*
脉搏异常 夜不能寐
*Pulse ain't right, I can't sleep at night*
这就是原囚
And here's the reason why*
小心点 恩哈特
Watch out, Earnhardt.
这可不是碰碰车
This ain't bumper cars.
真的很抱歉 等一下 艾琳
I am so sorry. Wait a minute, Irene.
可能我只是走太快了
I guess I was just going a little bit too fastl
-你没事吧 -没事
You alright? - Yeah.
你可真是神级赛车手
Mario Andretti over here.
医生无法确诊
*A doctor can't diagnose*
因为当心碎的时候
Cause when a heart starts to fall apart
听诊器是听不出来的
* You can't hear through the stethoscope*
我这是怎么了我说这很简单
* What's wrong with me? I said it's a simple fact*
我觉得你不会回来了
*I don't believe you're ever comin'back*
我为之倾倒
*I'mcomin'down, down*
*I'm comin'down, down*
倾倒
*Comin'down, down*
火 Comin' down, down*
倾倒
*I'm coming down, down*
大 Down, down, down*
乔伊斯 你能推我去厕所吗
Joyce, can you wheel me over to the shitter?
-你又要上厕所吗 -噫
You have to go again? Woman: Ugh.
动作快点
Hurry it up in there.
车到了
The bus is here.
动物又不会跑
The animals aren't going anywhere.
我们不能错过猩猩表演啊
We can't miss the orangutan show.
她可厉害了
She's very impressive.
贝蒂 魔术贴你都觉得厉害
Betty, you think Velcro is impressive.
我真的很高兴
I'm so glad
你回来了
you came back.
已经11点10分了 车要走了
It's 11: 10. The bus is going to leave.
我得上厕所 她到底在干什么
I got to piss. What the hell is she doing in there?
我也不知道怎么说
I don't know what to tell you people.
她腹泻
She has diarrhea.
到此为止 我受够了
That's it. I've had it.
车已经好了
Woman: The bus is ready.
贝蒂 贝蒂
Betty. Bettyl
很好
Oh. Good.
你要来帮我擦屁股吗
You gonna help me wipe?
我下面又裂了
Because my crevices have crevices.
-让让 -终于好了
Excuse me. Finally!
有什么入不了的
Big deal:
各位注意
Man: Attention.
请苔藓橡树养老院的客人们
Would our guests from Mossy Oaks retirement
到灵长动物区
please meet the zookeeper liaison
找动物园联系人
in the primate area.
梅兰妮要开始表演了
Melanie is performing now.
好 我觉得这很好
Joyce: Okay. I think this is good.
是这里吗 好
Right here? Okay. Irene: Hmm.
给 来吧
Here. Let's do this.
好了 你准备好了吗
Okay. You ready?
我准备好了
Yeah. I'm good.
-你看上去好像没准备好 -我只是 没事的
You don't look ready. - I'm just- - I'm good. Just- -
姐妹
Girl?
-你没事吧 -没事
You good? - Yeah, yeah, yeah.
快把这个拿掉
Take, take this off.
没脉搏了
I'm not getting a pulse.
走。快走
Man: Go, go!
充电
Charging.
离手
Clear.
And clear.
天 是谁啊
Oh dear, who is that?
新来的 312的 本
Uh, new guy from 312, Ben.
心脏病发
Heart attack.
是否存在完美谋杀呢
Narrator Does the perfect murder exist?
这就得问问猫头鹰了
This, I have asked the owls.
嘘
Fletchers: Shh!
-能之后再吸吗 -抱歉
Hey, do you mind? Sorry.
你不用管弗莱彻家的
Hey, hey, hey. Don't worry about the Fletchers.
弗莱彻家的是吧 谢了
Oh, the Fletchers. Thanks.
我得说 感觉他们挺硬核的
I got to say, they seem very hard- core.
哪里人啊 荷兰人吗
What are they, Dutch?
没有 他们只是喜欢看谋杀
No, just into murder,
很没礼貌
very rude.
我呢 我绝对不会跟一位女士说
Now, me, I would never tell a lady
不要吸
when to stop sucking.
搞什么 老兄
What the fuck, dude?
皮特
Betty: Pete,
别烦新来的小姑娘了来
stop pestering the new girl, come on.
别忘了要报名下周的动物园之旅
And don't forget to sign up for the zoo trip next week.
他好变态
That is a very pervy guy.
-他就是变态皮特 -怪不得
It's Pervy Pete. Explains it.
远离他和他的朋友
Betty: Steer clear of his entire gang,
农原体卡尔和淋病格雷格
Chlamydia Cal and Gonorrhea Greg.
都是变态
They're creeps.
至少人如其名 是吧
Well, at least truth in advertising, huh?
其实我觉得有衣原体的是格雷格
Actually, I think it's Greg that has Chlamydia.
就是冰岛和格陵兰岛那样反过来是吧
Aha. So, kind of an Iceland- Greenland scenario
这里的所有人所有事我都知道
I know everything about everyone who lives here.
跟紧我就好 我是贝蒂
Just stick with me. I'm Betty
希望不是肉毒杆菌贝蒂
Hopefully not Botulism Betty.
大部分人都意识不到
Betty: Most people don't realize all the things
压力锅多有用
you can do with an Instapot.
芝士蛋糕 丹佛鸡蛋卷
Cheesecake. Denver omelet.
我之前用了22分钟就做出了红葡萄酒洋葱烧牛肉
I once made a beef bourguignon in 22 minutes.
女士们 能不能
Ladies, would you please turn
把收音机音量关轻一点
your ghetto blaster down?
小心那两个
Watch out for these two.
她们是重刑犯
They're felons.
一还嗑药 一懂了
And junkies. - Right.
这儿可真是罪恶的巢穴
Ah. Real den of iniquity, this place.
不管你干什么记住
Whatever you do, stay away
远离乔伊斯和艾琳
from Joyce and Irene.
我不想知道
Charlie: Idon't want to know.
我真的不想
I really don t.
好糟糕哦
Ah! Irene: That was awful.
你们把我彻底打败了
You guys are trouncing me,
你们俩也太凶猛了
cause you are a pair of shuffle sharks.
你姿势不对 太紧张了
Your form is off. You're too tense
你得放松一点什么没有啊 我多放松啊
You need to loosen up. - What? No. I'm loose.
我整个人就是放松的 我不放松吗
That's my whole thing. Am I not loose?
你该试试愤怒治疗 那是什么
You should try rage therapy What's that?
感觉好爽
That shit feels good.
来 深呼吸
Hey, you, come on. Reach deep.
要从下体开始发力
It starts in the labia.
你知道吧
Mm- mm. You know.
我觉得
I think
我还是算了
that I'm fine with bottling
你们肯定不想看到我释放的
I- - you don't want to see me unbottled
你们接受不了我的释放
You can't, you can't handle the unbottled.
就是这玩意儿
Well, the thing that got us
让我们熬过了在贝德福德希尔斯的时候
through our stint at Bedford Hills.
是啊
Joyce: Yeah.
我靠 你们是真蹲过大牢啊
Crazy. You kids were really inside, huh? Upstate.
我们是政治犯
Joyce: We were political prisoners.
不开玩笑啊
Wow, no shit.
绝对不开玩笑
No shit whatsoever.
你们怎么惹上这种事儿的
Charlie: How'd you get into that?
我当时在读人学 时局动荡
I was in college. It was a turbulent time.
毕竟是60年代 你听见没
Oh yeah. I mean, the'60s. - Did you hear that?
那是70年代 小婊子 哦对
The 70s, bitch. - Charlie: Oh, right.
我市来还想说是90年代
You know, I was going to say the 90s
囚为你穿的这么多法兰绒
because of all the flannel
你最好是真的这么想
You'd have been better off going there.
真是抱歉
I'm so sorry,
只是两个吞世代和沙壶球游戏罢了
just a pair of tweens and a shuffleboard.
哇哦
Charlie: Whoa- whoa!
－艾琳 没错
- Irene! - Irene: Yeah, that's right
很正经啊
Very straight edge.
和我想的完全不一样
I mean, not at all what I was expecting.
在碰到我的守护恶魔之前
Yeah, I was on the straight and narrow
我可正派了
before I met my guardian devil.
一 什么 一是啊
What? - Yeah.
她当时在大路上
She was shouting down
大喊大叫地宣讲
some coeds on the quad,
我听到了她说的话
and I. heard what she was saying
给我打开了全新世界的大门
and my brain opened up.
在那之前世界显得那么不合理
World didn't make sense before that...
然后突然就合理了
and then it did.
这故事真是太可爱了
It's adorable.
她带我加入了组织
Irene: She brought me into the group.
改变了我的人生
Changed my life.
把我介绍给加布里尔
Introduced me to Gabriel.
哎哟喂
Ooh- la- la.
这个加布里尔又是谁 是谁
Who's this Gabriel? What, who's Gabriel?
这个组织就是加布里尔成立的
Gabriel started the group.
他招募了我
He recruited me and.
一训练我们 -启迪我们 -训练我们
...he trained us, inspired us. - Trained us.
他是我们的 指路明灯
He was our...he was our guiding light.
原来如此啊
I see what's happening here.
我猜他应该很有魅力
I'm getting a real magnetic vibe.
就像那种眼神迷死人的邪教领袖
Like a cult leader with pretty eyes.
他长得像塔吉特百货卖的那种
Ehh, he looked like one of those white guys
相框里的白人
you see in the picture frames that you buy from Target.
你说什么
Excuse me.
怎么了艾琳 派胡言 才不是
No excuse you. - Irene, you're nuts. Uh- uh.
拜托 加布里尔很性感
Excuse me. Gabriel was hot.
好吧 我中和一下你们的争议
Okay, I'm gonna split the diff.
这人应该像那种高中法语老师
I'm gonna picture my high school French teacher.
但有一件事我俩看法相同
One thing's for sure though...
他有个消防栓一样的大席
Both: Dick like a fire hydrant!
加布里尔真行啊 谁不喜欢这样的
Oh, good for Gabriel. Everyone enjoys it.
对长得好 加布里尔
Yes. Well done, Gabriel.
加布里尔不仅器大
Gabriel was more than that.
心地还好 他知道我们可以
You know, he, he knew that we could make
通过追究恶人
the world a better place
把世界变得更美好
if we hold the assholes to account.
你懂我意思吗
You feel me?
我懂 这就是加布里尔
- I feel you. That was Gabriel.
我懂你
I feel you, I'm- -
我完完全全理解你们在说什么
I am picking up what you're putting down.
我得承认好久没见过像你俩这么酷的
And I gotta say, you two are the coolest motherfuckers
牛逼姐妹儿了
I have met in a very long time.
真的抱歉爆粗了不然表达不出来
Seriously. I mean, sorry to curse, but necessary.
一没事 一之后发生了什么
what happened afterthat
他招募了你俩后 发生了什么
What happened after he recruited you?
我们就开始干大事了
We went to work.
稍等
*Hold on*
天 这么一听
Charlie: I got to say, it sounds like
我都觉得自己生不逢时了
I was born in the wrong time.
我们开始有了点名气
We were starting to get a reputation.
一个乐队还在他们的专辑封面上
A band even put our picture
使用了我们的照片
on the cover of their album,
色调消沉乐队
The Droopy Hues.
Charlie: The Droopy Hues.
天 这名字真烂
Gosh, what an awful name for a band.
-他们的歌怎么样 -烂透了
Were they any good? - Awful.
你是说 那种吗
You mean like
查莉 没错
Joyce: Uh, Charlie. Yes.
但 一起上吗
But...together.
哎唷 你们看《亢奋》长大的一代
Okay. The Euphorica generation
连这个都接受不了
can't handle the heat?
《亢奋》你们以为我多大
Euphoria? How old do you think I am?
别忘了给你的手环充电 艾琳
Don't forget to charge your heartcuff, Irene.
能不能别这么絮叨
And don't forget to take your head
气氛杀手 比利
out of the man's ass, Billy.
你知道你不住在这里吧
You know you don't live here, right?
那是伊莲的开衫吗
Is that Elaine's cardigan?
我是在失物招领处
You know what, I found it
找到的
in the, uh, the lost and found,
我得承认 那里真是个好地方
which I got to say is stellar.
有好多好东西
So much stuff in there.
嗯 那不是遗失物品
No, it's, uh, it's actually not lost.
她得了动脉瘤 是穿着那件衣服
Um, she had an aneurysm and died.
去世的
in that sweater.
是啊 一股红花油味
Yeah, it smells like Icy Hot
能闻出来她度过了美好的一生
and a life well lived.
她真是难以理喻
She's gone full Cocoon.
比利 你愿意娶给我吗
Irene: Billy, will you marry me?
嘿 比利 比利
Hey, Billy, Billy.
所以 你们一起生活 一起恋爱
So, you're living, you're loving,
一起改变世界
you're changing the world.
后来出了什么问题
What went wrong?
我们在计划一次最为直接的行动
Oh, we were planning our most direct action.
一场真正的革命
It was the real revolution.
我们要点燃整个世界
Joyce: We were gonna set the world on fire.
我们站在了风口浪尖
Irene: We were on the cusp.
走到那一步总是会这样对吧
That's when it always happens, right?
我们遭到了突袭
It was a raid.
你们就是
So that's how...
这样被捕的
that's how you got arrested?
他们的计划不是逮捕我们
Their plan wasn't to arrest us.
他们荷枪实弹就闯进来了
They came in there with guns blazing.
我们都想逃跑 但
We all tried to run, but...
艾琳
Irene.
艾琳太勇敢
Irene was brave.
她不想丢下加布里尔
She couldn't leave Gabriel behind.
你 趴地上 趴下
Officer: You, on the ground, on the ground!
嘿 看着我 有我在
Joyce: Hey, look at me, I got you.
我来帮你啦
Hey, I got you, okay.
－我的腿没知觉了 －有我在
Irene: I can't feel my legs. I got you.
我的腿没知觉了
Irene: I can't feel my legs.
我感觉不到我的腿
I can't feel my legs.
我感觉不到我的腿了
他们带走了一切 一切
They took, took everything.
我的腿
My legs...
我们的自由
our freedom.
和加布里尔
And Gabriel.
只希望他走得不痛苦
Just hope he didn't suffer.
但永远无人得知了
But we'll never know.
真是的 天啊 你们两个
Fucking Christ, man. You two.
失去了那么多 却仍选择勇往直前
AlI that loss and you keep moving forward,
继续自己的生活
living your lives.
看来还是要原谅和忘记 对吧
Forgive and forget, right?
哦 亲爱的
Irene: Oh, sweetie.
不
No.
我们从不原谅
We never forgive.
我们这有瑜伽 游泳
Billy: We have yoga, swimming,
普拉提 感兴趣都可以参与
Pilates, if that interests you.
好了 请您在这儿
Alright, if I can get your signature
签个名
right here.
最下面
Sign on the bottom.
我们在三楼为您安排予
Alright. We have you in a suite
一间套房 就在我们的医护区
on our third floor, our medical care unit
我可以带您参观下我们的设施
I can give you a full tour of the facilities
为您佩戴健康手环系统
and get you set up with our heartcuff system.
不过 我先让你们安顿一下
But, uh, I'll let y'all get settled in first.
好吧 还有什么
Okay, what else, what else, uh
你们准备妤去三楼了吗
okay, I think you guys are ready to come on up to the third floor.
咱们走吧 这样吧
Let's go! Actually
我让人帮您把行李送上去
I have someone to carry those bags for you.
查莉
Charlie!
好了 本叔
Alright, Uncle Ben,
我得先走了
I've got to hit the road.
我 诶
I, uh...
爱你
love you.
我是他侄子
I'm his nephew.
当然
Sure.
要我把窗户关上吗
Want me to, uh, close that window?
不 我喜欢冷一点
No, I like the cold
所以 你是哪里人昵
So, where are you from?
哪里也不是
Nowhere.
会有人来看望你吗
You got any visitors?
我可以跟前台说一下
Uh, cause I can let the front know,
这里很大 不好找
this place can be a real maze.
没有访客
I got no one.
好吧
Alright.
我把门带上
I'll get this.
欢迎您的入住
Welcome.
搭船去英国吧 宝贝
*Catch a boat to England, baby*
或许去西班牙
*Maybe to Spain*
无论我走到哪
*Wherever I have gone*
无论我走到哪里 去过哪里
*Wherever I've been and gone*
无论我走到哪里 忧郁
*Wherever I have gone, the blues*
与我常伴
*Are all the same*
加布里尔
Gabriel.
让人去买威士忌宝贝
*Send out for whisky, baby*
派人去买金洒
*Send out for gin*
我和客房服务 亲爱的
*Me and room service, honey*
我和客房服务宝贝
*Me and room service, babe*
哪怕亲眼看着你
Joyce: Even when I saw you,
我都不敢相信
I couldn't believe it.
我们俩都不相信
We both couldn't.
但我认得你的眼睛
But I knew your eyes.
这一刻我在脑子里想了好几年
I've thought about this moment for years,
想象着如果再见到你们
imagining what I'd do and what I'd say
我会做什么 说什么
if I ever saw you again.
现在终于找到了你们
And now that I finally found you
我无语凝噎了
I don't know.
早知道你活着 我们肯定会找你的
Joyce: We would have looked for you.
我们会找你一辈子
We never would have stopped looking.
我们以为你死了
We thought you were dead.
但你逃出来了
But you got away.
谢天谢地 你逃出来了
Thank God you got away.
无论我在哪里游戏
*Wherever I have played*
不管我何时掷出骰子
*Whenever I've throwed them dice*
无论我在哪里游戏
*Wherever I have played
忧郁
* The blues*
支配着整场游戏
*Have run the game*
也许明天吧 亲爱的
*Maybe tomorrow, honey*
也许路上的某一处
Someplace down the line*
一觉醒来 我会变老
*I'||I wake up older*
变得很 老妈妈
*So much older, mama*
一觉醒来 我会变老
*I'|l wake up older*
直到那一刻 我才会停止尝试
*And I'lI just stop all my tryin'*
我当时别无选择
Gabriel: I didn't have a choice.
事态已经失控了
Things had gotten out of hand,
而我阻止不了他们
and I, I couldn't stop them.
凭我一人之力不行
Not on my own.
我知道这是正确的抉择
I know I did the right thing.
但逼不得已 伤害我的爱人
But it kills me that I had to hurt
让我心如刀割
the ones I loved.
心如刀割
It kills you?
天 我们损失了
Man, we lost.
几十年的光阴
decades of our lives.
我失去了双腿
I lost my goddamn legs.
我知道
I know.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这就是我来这里的原因
That's why I'm here.
我一直会做一个梦
I have this dream
我看到
where I see.
你们俩在人群中我跟着你们
the two of you in a crowd, and I follow you.
走了好远好远 走到脚都流血了
For miles. For miles and miles until my feet bleed.
我努力解释
I try to explain myself.
但你们就是不回头
But you never turn around.
50年来
In 50 years
你俩从没回过头
you never turn around.
我意识到
And I realized that
如果不告诉你们真相
the dream would never change
这个梦我会一直做下去
until I told you the truth.
你们能原谅我吗
Can you please forgive me?
当然 加布里尔
Sure, Gabriel.
我们原谅你
We forgive you.
你和我想的一样吗
You thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
我们得杀了那个混蛋
We have to kill that motherfucker.
都11点10分了 车都要开了
It's 11: 10. The bus is going to leave.
我要尿尿 她在里面到底在干吗
I got to piss. What the hell is she doing in there?
我也不知道该跟你们怎么说
Look, I don't know what to tell you people.
她拉肚子了
She has diarrhea.
拉屎的事也能扯这么久 嗨起来了 女士们
Bullshitting about shitting Rock on, ladies. Great.
大巴已经准备好了
The bus is ready.
大家都上车 去动物园
AlI aboard for the zoo.
注意 请苔藓橡树
Man: Attention. Would our guests
养老院的客人
from Mossy Oaks Retirement please
嘿 你们好 我差点忘了
Hey, ladies. I almost forgot.
来看看
Check it out.
这是我在爱织上买的
I scored it on Etsy.
色调消沉
Droopy Hues
好吧 谁来给我指指 哪个是加布里尔
Okay, let's settle this Which one is our friend Gabriel?
人跟我想的不一样
Not what I was expecting.
但席的规格你们是一点没夸张
But you did not over hype the D- train.
是啊
Yeah. Yeah. - Uh...
好嘞 你们想去看猩猩表演吗
Alright, so you guys coming to see this chimp show?
不 我们就不去了
No, you know, we're. going to pass on it.
我们嗯 我们过敏
We, uh, we have an allergy.
对猴子毛过敏
To monkey dander.
-是的 -尽瞎扯
Irene: Yeah. - Ah. Bullshit.
骗错人了
And big mistake.
祝你们嗑药愉快
Enjoy gettin high.
那就出来见咯
And catch you on the flipside.
-出来见 宝贝 -好的 女士们
On the flipside baby. Alright, ladies.
来吧 从这里下去
Irene: Let's go, down here.
我来看你了 黑猩猩
Charlie: Wait for me, chimpanzee.
现在 梅兰妮
Now, Melanie,
能告诉我现在几点了吗
can you tell me what time it js?
两点23
2: 23.
-真棒 -哇塞
Excellent! - Wow!
太神奇了
That's arnazing.
天啊
Oh man.
乔伊斯和艾琳错过了一场好戏
Joyce and Irene are really missing out.
变态女同
Deviants.
假正经
Very uptight.
我们走了还不到半天
We weren't even gone half a day.
这次是什么人
What was it this time?
哦 新来的本
Oh, new guy. Ben.
-该死 -借过
Oh shit Uh, excuse me.
天
Man!
本是谁
Who was Ben?
这个问题
That's a,
我们每个人都
that's a question for each of us
有自己的答案
to answer for ourselves.
所以
And so,
让我们默哀片刻
let us take a moment of silence
来回顾市的一生
to reflect on Ben's life
以及他对我们每个人的意义
and what he meant to each of us.
嘿 假侄子
Psst. Hey, fake nephew.
节哀顺变 往旁边坐坐
Sorry for your loss, man. Scoot over.
你为什么
Why are you.
我是他的亲侄子
I'm a real nephew.
听着 我才不在乎你为什么要撒谎
Oh. Listen, I don't care why you're lying.
如果他是你的
You know, if it was
甜心老爹之类的
a sugar daddy situation or whatever,
-不是 -哦
It wasn't Oh.
他就是我叔
He was my uncle.
噢 甜心怪蜀黍
Oh, sugar uncle?
正常叔叔 啥甜不甜的
Regular uncle. No sugar.
你不是那个护工吗
Aren't you, like, the bellhop?
你又不认识他 你来干嘛
You didn't know him. Why are you here?
他就是 看起来挺伤心的
Well, he just, he seemed sad.
一个亲人都没有
Like, he didn't have anyone, you know.
我想至少我可以来送他一程
I figured I could show up here at least,
你知道的
you know.
其实呢 我市不该告诉你
The truth is, oh, I mean, I shouldn't tell you this,
但反正他已经死了 所以可能
but he's dead now, so it's probably
市参加了证人保护计划 我是负责他的特工
Ben was in witness protection. I was his case agent.
-哇 真的吗 -是啊
Wow. No shit. - Hmm.
所以你是联调局的了
So you're, like, FBI?
严格说来是的
Technically. I mean, yes, I am.
只不过
It's just
我以为自己会去打击恐怖分子
I thought I'd be, you know, fighting the war on terror.
结果现在帮一个老男人买杂货
Instead, I'm getting groceries for guys
他证词的年龄都比我大
whose testimony was relevant before I was born.
白瞎了我流利的乌尔都语
Never mind that Im fluent in fucking Urdu.
-厉害 -是啊
Oh wow. Yeah.
谢谢你们
Thank you.
所以 他是黑手党吗
So was he, like, Mafia?
他于了杀人越货的事
Did he do wet work?
我不能透露更多了
I've said too much already.
咦这人怎么看起来这么面熟
Gosh, where do I know this guy from?
他上过电视吗
Was he on TV or something?
应该没有吧
I don't think so.
消防栓
Fire hydrant.
知道了 知道了
Uh- oh. Uh- oh.
-色调下沉 -啥下沉
Droopy Hues. - Droop- What?
这是加布里尔 有屌为证
Yeah, that's Gabriel. Look at his dick.
是啊 什么 你怎么知道的
Y- yes. What? How do you know that?
不是瞎吹哈 我跟两个酷老姐们儿
Well, not to brag, but I'm friends
乔伊斯和艾琳是好朋友
with these pretty super cool chicks,
她们就住在这里
Joyce and Irene, who live here,
还跟我讲过她们的浪漫史呢
and they were telling me about their old flame.
-天啊乔伊斯·卡特和艾琳·斯莫斯
Ow, dude. - Joyce Carter and Irene Smothers.
对 乔伊斯和艾琳
Yes, Joyce and Irene.
乔伊斯·卡特和艾琳·斯莫斯也在这
Joyce Carter and Irene Smothers are here?
我们关系很好 一起搓麻 为什么
Yeah, they're my buds. We Mahjong. Why?
倾倒
*Comin'down*
乔伊斯 艾琳
Joyce, Irene.
我是联邦调查局的卢卡·克拉克探员
Special Agent Luca Clark, FBI.
跟我走一趟吧
Come with me, please.
我要倒下 倒下 倒下了
*I'mcoming down, down, down, down, down*
心痛欲绝地倒下了
*Coming down with a heartache*
查莉
Luca: Charlie.
她们使用非法药物
Betty: They use illegal drugs.
在安静时间大声喧哗
They have zero respect for quiet time.
在动物园时
And at the zoo,
她俩在玩什么性爱电击
they were doing some kind of sexual zapping.
彼得生日派对时
And at Peters birthday party,
她俩都吃了两块蛋糕
they both had two pieces of cake.
我一块都没吃到
And I, I didn't get any.
女士 谢谢您分享这么多
Yes, ma'am. Thank you for sharing
有用信息给我们
all of this very helpful information.
她俩绝不是好人
Those two are no good.
搁这当道德警察呢
What a fucking cop.
所以通过健康手环确定 本去世时
Okay, so the heartcuff data pins the time of death
乔伊斯和艾琳都在动物园
when Joyce and Irene were at the zoo,
所以加布里尔不是他们杀的
so they didn't kill Gabriel.
你直接来问我不就完了
Well, I could have told you that.
一般来讲 一位被保护证人见到
Well, normally, if someone in witness protection meets
指认的对象后
the people he, you know, witnessed
又离奇死亡
and then suddenly drops dead
你是说本或者加布里尔
Wait, are you saying that Ben or Gabriel or whatever,
就是当年出卖她们的人
he's the guy that ratted them out.
天 我真蠢
Oh God. I'm just so, so dumb.
他说想要转来这里
He said he wanted to transfer here,
我一点功课都没做说 就说
and I said, "Mossy Oaks. Sounds nice. "
“苔藓橡树”听起来不错
O I did zero research whatsoever.
是啊 是不够细心
Oh, yes. No, that is not very thorough.
但你也不用太自责
But, uh, don't beat yourself up
毕竟 人不是她们杀的
Cause guess what, they didn't kill him.
时间地点都对不上
I mean, with the zoo and the time
我认识她们
and I know them,
两人都是酷大姐
these guys are cool as shit.
不会做出那种事儿
Okay? They are not murderers.
查莉 乔伊斯和艾琳才不是酷大姐
Charlie, Joyce and Irene are not cool as shit.
她们是国内恐怖分子
They're domestic terrorists.
得了吧 这位先生
Alright, Mr. Man.
知道他们被抓时
Do you know what they were planning
-在做什么吗 -知道
when they were arrested? Yeah, I do.
她们在策划一场人游行之类的
They were doing some kind of a big march or something. So that's, uh...
他们打算用炸弹
There were going to blow up a meeting
搞砸一场
of the Model United Nations
模拟联合国会议
with bombs they made out of
用高压锅炸弹
: pressure cookers.
等等 你是说她们想
Huh. Wait, I'm sorry, they were going
炸掉联合国
to blow up the UN?
模拟联合国
The Model UN.
是高中生为了赚学分
As in high schoolers pretending
搞的一种模拟会
to be the UN for extra credit.
这性质就没那么恶劣吧
Okay. Is that better or worse?
毕竟不是真的联合国 对吧
Because, I mean, that's not the real UN, right?
性质更恶劣了
It's so much worse. They...
她们想用炸弹
They were going to kill children
炸死孩子
with explosives.
-惨绝人寰 -是啊
Yikes. Yeah.
-要是你遇到危险 -是啊
Anything comes up. - Yeah...
-你还是留着吧 -我不需要
You should keep that. I don't need that.
也许她们没杀加布里尔
Maybe they didn't kill Gabriel,
但你自己要小心 查莉
but watch your back Charlie.
这两个女人极其危险
Those two women are extremely dangerous.
掀翻三观了
- That was intense.
我以为自己在演《华尔街之狼》
I felt like I was in"Wolf of Wall Street"
还不是搞笑的那部分
all of a sudden and not the fun parts.
你是老鼠（告密者）吗 查莉
Are you a rat, Charlie?
什么
Eh?
他们拷问了我们一个小时
They grilled us for an hour.
你知道我们不喜欢猪（警察）
And you know we hate pigs.
和老鼠
And rats.
嘿嘿嘿
Hey, hey, hey.
我也不喜欢猪和老鼠
I hate pigs and rats, too.
还有蛇（小人）
And snakes.
中国生肖有一半我都不喜欢
Half the Chinese zodiac is no good in my book.
两位 我还是我 查莉
Hey, guys, it's me, okay. It's Charlie.
我跟那人接触前不知道他是联调局的
I didn't know the guy was a fed until we started talking.
他突然就告诉了我
He just sprung it on me.
我不是告密的
BAYL} I'm no stoolie.
我要是知道市是谁
If I had known who Ben was,
我会离他远远的
I would have steered clear.
等等 你们为什么不直接告诉我
Wait, why didn't you just tell me,
本就是加布里尔
you know, that, that Ben was Gabriel?
你觉得我们会作何感受
How do you think we feel? o
有天房门突然被敲开
Knocks on our door the other night, says,
那人说 我还活着 我背叛了你们俩
hey, I'm alive, and I betrayed you both.
对啊 那次什么情况
Geez. How'd that go?
我们告诉他 我们原谅他了
We told him we forgave him.
那就好
Hah. Good.
原谅了 是啊
Forgiveness. Alright.
对了 有件事我挺想问问你们的
Oh, uh, I did want to ask you guys about this,
听起来有点疯狂 也许不是啥大事
this crazy thing, it's probably nothing.
很明显 你们当初打算
So apparently, you guys were going to,
炸掉一个儿童版的
I don't know, blow up some kind of
联合国之类的
United Nations for babies or something.
查莉 你一定要知道
Charlie, what you have to understand
上预科精英学校的学生
about these elite prep school kids,
他们都是当权
they were the offspring
法西斯分子的后代
of the reigning fascists of the day.
我们想给下一代的战争罪犯
Joyce: And we wanted to send a message
表明一下态度
to the next generation of war criminals. o
明白了
I see.
我再问问清楚哈
Just to be crystal clear here,
你们是真的要
so, uh...we're talking about...
用炸弹炸死
blowing up high school kids?
高中生吗
Like, with bombs?
当时时代不一样
It was a different time.
好吧
Alright.
我不得不承认
I got to say, I really feel like
我们之前略去了很多细节
we glossed over some details here.
你知道自己听上去
You know who you're beginhing
越来越像谁吗
to sound a lot like?
-贝蒂 -贝蒂
Betty. Betty.
好吧
Right.
我也不得不说
I got to say, you know,
你俩听上去越来越像曼森
you're starting to sound a lot less like Hoffman
而不是霍夫曼呢
and a lot more like Manson, so
该死
Oh shit.
等等
Wait, uh,
你们俩
did you guys
真的杀了本吗
Did you kill Ben?
你带窃听器了吗 查莉
You wearing a wire, Charlie?
喂 煞笔探员 滚犊子吧
Hey, Agent Fuckface. Go suck an egg.
别这样吼我的胸
念 Alright, man, stop talking to my tits.
你们知道吗
You know what? I
真的是 我以为你俩是一对儿
Fuck! I just I really thought you guys were, like,
酷姐妹儿呢
these two super- cool women.
你们说了那么多
You know, all this talk about
为信仰而战
standing up for what you believe in
让混蛋付出代价的话
and holding the assholes accountable
原来 你们才是大混蛋
You're the assholes.
懂了
Got it.
你和我想的一样吗
You thinkin' what I'm thinkin'?
那是斯卡加尔德吗
Fletcher 1: Is that a Skarsgard?
你看谁都像斯卡加尔德
Fletcher 2: You think everyone is a Skarsgard.
谁让他们长得那么帅
Well, everyone is a Skarsgard.
嘿你们看了很多犯罪谋杀剧对吗
Hey hey, you guys watch a lot of murder shows, right?
小声点
Fletchers: Shh!
抱歉 真的对不起
I'm sorry. I'm very sorry
我想问问
Uh, I was just wondering, um,
你们知道有什么容易购买
do you know of any easily accessible poisons
还能不知不觉引发心脏病的毒药吗
that would trigger an undetectable heart attack?
氯化钾
Potassium chloride.
第三季《莉莉花庄园》的标准套路
Standard go- to, third season"Lillyflay Manor. "
氯化钙
Calcium chloride.
肾上腺素
Epinephrine.
硝酸钠
Sodium nitrate.
常见的花肥
Common gardening ingredient.
当然什么都比不上
Of course, it's hard to top
蓖麻毒素
ricin.
是的呢 蓖麻毒素
AlI Fletchers: Ooh, ricin
那你们刚说的那个花肥呢
Eh, what about the, the gardening one?
Oh sure.
几毫升硝酸钠
Couple of cc's of sodium nitrate
老天爷都救不回来
and you're deader than dirt.
最棒的是
And the best thing is
这是人体天然的化合物
it's a naturally occurring compound in the body.
你要想靠尸检找到这玩意儿
Trying to find that in an autopsy,
根本不可能
forget about it.
不错 花肥
Right on. Gardening.
行行行 你们继续
Okay. Okay. As you were.
硝酸钠
Sodium nitrate.
应该就是这个了
Yeah, I guess so.
如果她是
If that's what she, uh,
用这个来种入麻
uses for her ganja situation.
天 她都拿这个干什么了
Man, what's she been doing with it?
我周一给了她一周的量
I gave her a week's worth on Monday,
周三又给了一周的量
then another week's worth on Wednesday.
你跟她说别嗑太狠了
You tell her don't shoot that stuff.
会出问题的
It'll mess you up.
-假侄子 -查莉 嗨
Charlie: Fake nephew. - Charlie. Hey.
听着 如果我
So listen, ifI, uh
我有一些信息
if I had some information
和本的死有关的 这种事
about Ben's death, is that something,
你能保证不把我牵扯进来吗
like, could you keep my name out of the whole business?
可以我就是 我就是干证人保护这一行的
Yes, that's what I- - my job is literally witness protection.
我发现乔伊斯
It turns out that Joyce had access
在本被杀前一天拿到了硝酸钠
to some sodium nitrate the day before Ben was killed.
你最近保护的人被干掉了啊
Man: Oh. Your last guy got whacked?
什么情况 我这
What is that? Am I, uh...
你是给我开外放了吗
Sorry, am I on speakerphone?
对 不是 那是公牛吉诺
Yes. No, that's Gino the Bull.
可能那都不是谋杀
It probably wasn't even murder.
可能 马龙
Probably? Marone
你这样我也不会
this ain't inspiring
对你有信心的啊
a lot of confidence, you know.
查莉 她们要怎么用硝酸钠
Luca: Charlie, how could they have killed him
来杀掉他啊
with sodium nitrate?
死亡时间是2点23分
Time of death was 2: 23.
她们当时和你一起在动物园
They were at the zoo with you.
2点23分
2: 23.
2 3 4 我靠
Two- two- three. Whoa!
兄弟 那是猴子的时间
Whoa, dude, dude, that's the time of the monkey.
什么的什么
What of the what?
就是动物园的猴子
Oh, th- th- th- the monkey at the zoo.
那个表演 它能表演说时间
The show, you know, it tells time.
梅兰妮 是梅兰妮 她可厉害了
Melanie. Melanie. She's amazing.
我看表演的时候
And when I saw this show,
猴子说的时间就是2点23分
the time the monkey told was 2: 23.
这也太巧了吧
That's a weird coincidence, huh?
就是说
Uh, I mean,
你觉得她会不会
do you think that maybe she's, uh...
她会不会有某种猴子预知能力
you think she's some kind of a monkey pre- cog?
预知能力 你是说猴子版的《少数派报告》吗
Pre- cog. Like"Minority Report" with monkeys?
我不是这么觉得
No, I do not.
但那部电影我还挺想看的
I would watch that movie, though.
等等等等 不是
Charlie: Wait, wait, wait. No.
乔伊斯和艾琳她们没看表演
So, Joyce and Irene, they skipped the show.
操 对啊 她们可以
Fuck, yes, they could have...
靠 不对 她们没时间开车回来
Ah shit, no, it's not enough time for the drive,
但她们可能伪造了死亡时间
but maybe they faked the time of death.
查莉 记得我怎么说那俩人的吗
Luca: Charlie, remember what I said about those two?
-小心她们俩 -比利
Be careful with those two- - - Yeah. Hey, Billy!
我等会儿给你回电话
Let me call you back, okay.
比利 你好
Billy. Hey, how you been?
我想问能不能
I was wondering, could I get a quick peek
看看本的手环数据呢
at the data from Ben's robo- arm- bracelet?
不行 那就违反健保与责任法案了
No, absolutely not. That'd be a HIPAA violation.
行 虽然我听不懂你说啥
Oh yeah, and I'm hip- a to what you're saying.
但就这一次行吗
But, uh, maybe just this once
好吧
Okay.
-我不该怎么干的 但还是行吧 -谢谢你
I shouldn't be doing this, but okay. - Thank you.
你看 这是全部记录
Look, you can see the whole story.
他的心率在2点23分飙升
He had a cardiac spike at 2: 23,
z40
然后体征就没了
and then the vitals just stopped.
oP
在那之后 我们试图给他除颤
And after that, we tried to defib him,
但他已经死了
but he was already gone.
我问你件事 这有没有可能
Let me ask you something, is it possible to, uh,
是伪造的
I don't know, fake this?
这能不能被篡改啊
Like, could you go in and change it?
不行 这数据没法改
No, no, it's hard data. - Huh.
这个 11点10分的小变化是什么
What's this, this blip at 11: 10?
-可能他被吓到了 -不 你看
Billy: Maybe he was startled. Charlie: No, but look.
我是说心率变了
I mean, the heartbeat, it changes.
速度和力量都不一样
I mean, it's a different speed, strength.
好像换了颗心脏一样
It's almost like he switched hearts or something.
好奇怪
That is weird.
TZU
58 81 58 I
11点10分
Charlie: 11: 10
58 81 120
正好是我们出发
That's right around when we were leaving
去动物园的时候
for the zoo.
她拉屎的事都扯了半天
She bullshitted about shitting.
卢卡 你准备好听顶级推理了吗
Alright, Luca, are you ready for some grade- A figuring?
她顺着植物架爬了上去
So she climbed up the plant ladder,
换掉了手环 在11点10分杀了他
swapped out the heartcuff, killed him at 11: 10.
然后她爬了下来 去了动物园
Then she climbed back down, went to the zoo,
然后在猴子表演韵时候假装了心率飙升
and faked the cardiac spike during the monkey show.
-乒乓嘭 -是乒啪嗒嘭
Bing- bang- boom. - Bing- bada- boom.
-这太疯狂了 -但是有可能
- It's nuts. - Charlie: But plausible.
可能也不能帮我们申请到逮捕令啊
Plausible's not grounds for an arrest warrant.
要我信你并行动
I need something hard and firm
我需要切实的证据
ifI'm going to ride this one.
现在我们才有得聊
Now you're speaking my language.
还有 查理 如果你说的是对的
Luca: Also, Charlie, for this theory to work,
那乔伊斯或者艾琳
either Joyce or Irene would have needed
需要制造出心脏病发的假象
to simulate a heart attack.
我看了飙升的心率图
I looked at that spike.
这不是单纯开合跳跳就能有的
That isn't doing jumping jacks.
那是真的心脏病发
That's a real cardiac event.
我不知道这要怎么假装
I don't know how you fake that.
我等会儿给你回电话
I gotta get back to you.
皮特 我问你个问题
Heya, Pete, uh, let me ask you a question.
你懂性爱电击的事吗
Do you know anything about sexual zapping?
你说的这是电击情趣
You speak of electro- play.
好变态的 我绝对不要
Kinky stuff. Not for the faint of heart.
你只需要一个电击枪 还有开放的心态
AII you need is a taser and an open mind.
-嗨 -贝蒂
Hello? Charlie: Uh, Betty.
是你老朋友查莉
Uh, it's your old friend Charlie.
有什么事
Oh. What do you want?
听着 我觉得你说的
Oh, listen, I think you might have been right
乔伊斯和艾琳的事没错
about, uh, Joyce and Irene.
我早说了
Betty: I told you.
-又是重刑犯又是瘾君子 -我知道
Felons and junkies. Charlie: Yeah, yeah, I know.
听着 我需要知道你在动物园看到了什么
Listen, I, I need to know what you saw at the zoo.
你提到了一个什么性爱电击
You mentioned something about a sexual zapping.
对
Betty: Well, yes.
我当时正在像正常人一样买帽子
I was buying a hat like a normal person
然后我看到乔伊斯和艾琳鬼鬼祟祟的
when I saw Joyce and Irene looking extra suspicious.
她们在暖房里给彼此安慰
They were in the hothouse pleasuring each other
用某种电动老二
with some kind of electro- dildo.
更糟糕的是我错过了猴子表演
And the worst of it is I missed the monkey show,
我就是为了那个表演
which was the whole reason that I organized
才组织去动物园的
the trip in the first place.
贝蒂 这就对了 我们抓到她们了
Betty, that's it. That's it. I think we got'em.
我好开心终于有人听我说了
I'm glad somebody is finally listening.
我今早就跟艾琳说了
Like I told Irene this morning,
你不能在动物园
"The zoo is no place
玩那些变态的SM技巧
"to practice your twisted masochistic fetishes,
联邦调查局的人会知道的
and the FBI will hear about it.
等等 贝蒂 你和艾琳说了吗
Wait, Betty, you told Irene all this.
一个小时以前啊
Uh, just an hour ago.
等一下 查莉
Hold on just a minute, Charlie.
我的压力锅的声音好奇怪等等
My Instapot is making funny noises. Hold on.
压力锅 别别别 贝蒂
Pressure cooker. No, no, Betty.
贝蒂 你得赶紧离开
Betty, you got to get out of there.
贝蒂 贝蒂
Betty! Betty!
快走
Evacuate!
你好蠢
Joyce: You're so silly.
-我的天 -我的天
Irene Oh God. - Joyce: Oh, my God.
我觉得我们可能太冒险了
Ooh I think we may be pushing our luck.
你准备好换换景色了吗
You up for a change of scenery?
你觉得玻利维亚那里
Look, you think they got, uh, senior
有养老院吗
living in Bolivia?
查莉
Charlie.
你有事吗
How can we help you?
贝蒂全都告诉我了
Betty told me everything,
她看到你们俩
uh, about how she saw you two
在暖房里电击彼此
tasing each other in the hothouse.
你们就是这样骗到了护士
That's how you tricked the nurses into thinking
让他们以为本心脏病发了
that Ben was having a heart attack
但他其实已经死了好几个小时了
uh, when he'd really been dead for hours
很聪明 但你们漏过了一个小细节
Pretty clever. But you missed one detail.
什么小细节
What might that be?
本的心率监控器在你们
Ben's heart monitor recording went totally flat
在2点23分玩了电击之后
after your tasing stunt
就彻底平了
at 2: 23.
猴子的时间
The time of the monkey.
但是护士们曾经试图给他除颤
But the nurses tried to revive him with a defibrillator.
如果他当时带着的真的是自己的手环
If he'd really been wearing his heartcuff monitor,
那应该会记录下电击
it would have registered those shocks.
你还挺会说
Ain't that some shit. - Mm- hmm.
你说这么多就为了那个
And all this for a motherfucker
让我们蹲了30年大牢的混蛋吗
who sent us to prison for 30 years?
你们当时就是罪有应得
You deserved it then
现在依然是
and you deserve it now.
收好你们的沙壶球吧 女士们
Wax up your shuffleboard pucks, ladies.
等我把这事儿告诉我的
As soon as I tell my new FBI buddy
新联邦调查局朋友
about all this, well
你们马上就要回去蹲大牢了
Yeah, man, you're going right back to Bedford.
所以这些你还没告诉他吗
So you haven t told him all of this yet?
搞什么
Charlie: The fuck?
婊子
Ah! - Joyce: Bitch!
操
Joyce: Fuck!
死婊子
Irene: Fucking bitch.
该死的八零后
Fucking millennial.
我是90后你个变态
I'm a cusper, you fucking psycho.
我是不会对小老太太下手的
And I draw the line at fighting little old ladies.
我们在牢里都是这么打架的 小婊子
That's how we did it in Bedford, bitch.
搞什么
What the fuck!
我他妈要杀了你 小婊子
I'll fucking kill you, you motherfucker.
你居然喷我 小婊子
You talc'd me, you fucking whore.
-赶紧去拿毒药 -好好好
Get the fucking poisonl- Joyce: Yeah, yeah, yeah.
按住她
Keep her held down.
赶紧 杀了她
Come on, move.
就这儿 对
Right there. Yeah.
我操
Oh! Fuck. -
-别 -你想都别想
Irene: Oh no! - Joyce: Don't you try it.
你他妈想都别想
Don't you fucking try it.
放下 放下
Irene: Put it down. Put it down.
放下
Down!
我觉得我们把她弄坏了
Uh, I think we broke her.
赶紧完事儿
Let's get this shit done.
我靠
Oh shit. Yeah.
-谢天谢地 -靠
Charlie: Oh, thank God. - Irene: Oh, shit.
操
Joyce: Oh, fuck.
住手
Stop right there. Stop.
好厉害的条子
What a fuckin' cop.
行吧
Alright.
你又来了
Here you come again*
你说你是我的朋友
*And you say that you're my friend*
但我知道你的目的
*But I know why you're here
她想知道我的感受
She wants to know how I feel*
告诉她我很开心
Tell her that I'm happy*
查莉·凯尔 你的直觉很准
Well, Charlie Cale, you have great instincts.
有没有想过加入联邦调查局
You ever think about joining the FBI?
我其实不是很乐于助人
Well, I'm not really about helping the man.
对了 你们有没有收到
Although, uh, did you guys ever get my email
我发的关于卡齐米尔·凯恩的邮件呢
about, uh, Kazimir Caine?
你们是指谁
"You guys meaning who?
FBI@FBI.gov
FBI at FBI dot gov.
我都不知道这是不是存在
I don't even know if that's a thing,
但邀约依然成立
but the offer stands.
你要是哪天愿意了 随时联系我
You ever get in a jam, you have my number.
没问题
Toodles.
天啊
Oh God.
坚持住 恩戈齐家族
*Hold on, Ngozi Family*
我们是一支厚重的赞比亚乐队
*We are a Zambian band with a heavy sound*
坚持住 恩戈齐家族
*Hold on, Ngozi Family*
我们是一支厚重的赞比亚乐队
*We are a Zambian band with a heavy sound*
听好了宝贝
*Listen, baby*
我已经在这里
*I've been in the country*
stunt utility ZACK ROBERTS
待了一辈子了
*Since I was born a long time ago*
我收到了很多信
*I had lots of letters*
邀请我们去演出
*Requesting where we could go*
现在我们每次
*Now every time*
全国巡演
*We tour in the country*
坚持住 恩戈齐家族
*Hold on, Ngozi Family*
我们是一支厚重的赞比亚乐队
*We are a Zambian band with a heavy sound*
visual eftects compositor AMIT_P, UJARI
坚持住. 恩戈齐家族
*Hold on, Ngozi Family*
我们是一支厚重的赞比亚乐队
We are a Zambian band with a heavy sound
*We are a Zambian band with a heavy sound*